ARTURO CARCAMO

Boca Raton, FL, 33433 | (C) (561) 955-0147 | arturocarcamo1@gmail.com Open to relocation to Seattle and New York

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software engineer successful at working with teams, driving progress toward project milestones, with quality assurance and on-time delivery. Experienced at creating data regression models, collecting, analyzing and interpreting large datasets, using predictive data modeling, and analyzing data mining algorithms to deliver insights and implement action-oriented solutions to problems.

SKILLS

- C and C++
- Python
- Java
- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript
- Dart (Flutter)
- Fast learner
- Analytical and critical thinker

- Dependable
- Skilled multi-tasker Data Visualization & Predictive Analysis
- Data Analytic, Model Development & Machine Learning Algorithms
- Organized
- · Excellent attention to detail

EDUCATION

Florida Atlantic University, Boca Raton FL,

May 2018

- Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering
- Bachelor of Science: Computer Science
- Coursework in Web Design and Development Computational Science and Software Engineering
- 3.5 GPA

May 2020

- Master of Science: Computer Science Florida
- Coursework in Data Analytics, AI, Natural Language Processing, and machine learning
- Big Data Analytics Certificate
- 3.7 GPA

WORK HISTORY

March 2017 - Present

Software QA Engineer Intern / Trivantis, Inc. | Deerfield Beach, FL

Designs and maintain software for QA automation using Selenium. Performs regression and system-level testing to verify software quality and function before it is released. Collaborates with product management to design, build and test systems. Drafts comprehensive reports to document bugs and design flaws.

SEPTEMBER 2015-JANUARY 2017

Technician / Fixology | 7036 W Palmetto Park Rd

AUGUST 2011-SEPTEMBER 2015

Electronics team member / Target | 3599 W Hillsboro Blvd

ACADEMIC RESEARCH AND PROJECTS

Detecting Skin Cancer with Deep Learning – Miguel Potolicchio, Arturo Carcamo, Dominic Cassisa

Research and development of convolutional neural network in the medical field to achieve improvements in accuracy in shorter time. CNN was created with custom layers for image classification. Programmed in R using academic test and train datasets.

Toto: Smart Pet Feeder

Mobile application developed in Dart using Flutter for iOS and Android with Firebase database backend and Raspberri Pi with Node-RED. Integration of multiple sensors with Raspberry Pi hardware and software development of web application.

Cyber Security: Measurement and Data Analysis

Application developed to read and analyse files that contain the packet data of a network, for deep analysis and visualization.

Data Science

Data analytics and statistical analysis of large datasets. Programmed applications in Python using NumPy, Pandas, Matplotlib, scikit-learn and other libraries. Experienced with representative datasets and problems in data science and machine learning

Information Retrieval and Natural Language Processing

Programmed applications for text indexing, text processing, web search and text mining.

BILINGUAL

English Spanish